Miss, didn't you go to the teahouse?
Why are you back so soon?
Teahouse?
I just came out of the palace.
I didn't go to any teahouse.
But someone just came to the mansion
and said Miss had urgent business with Young Master,
asking him to find you at the teahouse.
Miss.
Brother.
You're here.
You're really here.
Who told you to look for me at the teahouse?
Why do you seem a bit strange?
What happened?
What are you doing?
You killed Father,
causing the PM's Mansion to fall into this situation.
I'll kill you
to avenge father!
What are you talking about?
I am Sui'er!
I will kill you
to avenge father!
Kill you! Avenge!
Avenge!
Brother!
Kill you! Avenge!
What are you talking about?
Why do you say I killed our father?
Brother.
I'll kill you.
Are you okay?
What a touching play of brother and sister
turning against each other.
Shen Suhe.
You like acting the most.
Are you satisfied
with this play I've arranged?
Ling Chuchu,
what did you do to my brother?
I found something
in the secret chamber.
I heard him say
he used it to control Shen Yi,
so I thought I'd try it on your brother.
I didn't expect that in just a few minutes,
your brother would be at my command.
Taro powder?
How can there be taro powder?
So it's taro powder.
My brother has no grudges against you.
Why did you do this?
Shen Suhe,
thanks to you,
I lost everything.
If you don't let me live,
I won't let you live, either.
Ling Chuchu,
you've insulted me in every way before,
but as long as you don't hurt my family,
I can let bygones be bygones
and spare your life.
Now that you're so ruthless,
then go to hell with Mu Jinghao.
Brother, save me.
Brother.
You have to avenge me.
She's gonna kill me!
Brother!
I didn't mean to!
I'm Sui'er!
Brother!
Sui'er?
You know me?
Let my brother go!
Eat it,
and I'll let your brother go.
How about that?
You...
Don't come over.
Or I'll kill him.
If I eat this,
will you let him go?
Don't you do anything for your family?
What?
Are you afraid of death now?
Death?
I've died many times.
so I'm not afraid of death.
I've eaten it.
Now can you let my brother go?
Shen Suhe,
I'll make you suffer.
I'll make you watch the people you love
die one by one because of you.
What do you mean?
I got you into this.
No.
Brother.
Sui'er.
I got you into this.
No.
Shen Suhe,
you're a disaster.
[Your mother,]
[father, brother,]
[the whole residence,]
[and the Second Prince,]
[they all died because of you.]
[It's you.]
[You killed them.]
[You must live on,]
[in endless pain.]
Brother,
why did you do this?
it's my fault.
Sui'er.
Sui'er,
it's not your fault.
I was the one who fell for her.
It's not your fault.
I can't protect you anymore.
You must live well,
For me,
for father,
for mother,
live a good life.
Brother.
Is it really because of me?
Watch out!
Your mother,
father,
brother, the entire mansion,
[and His Highness]
[all died because of you.]
[It's you.]
[You killed them.]
[You must live on,]
[in endless]
[agony.]
I killed them.
Sui'er.
It's me.
Sui'er
It's my fault.
I'm sorry
for your brother.
Your Highness
Can I be alone for a while?
Okay.
I'll wait for you outside.
How is she?
Sui'er,
are you still mad at me?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
If we're to blame,
it's all because I provoked Ling Chuchu,
which led to this situation.
It has nothing to do with you.
Then why...
Your Highness,
we just met by chance.
You don't have to
ask about my business.
Shen Suhe.
Do you think
I'm useless?
I don't.
Then why do you think
you can
come and go as you please?
Yes.
I got involved with you first.
All my people are dead.
If you don't want to die,
leave me
as far as possible.
Shen Suhe,
you have provoked me.
I won't let you go.
Your Highness,
I'm dying.
I have my own things to do.
I have no time to be entangled with you.
Please let me go.
A dying person?
How many secrets do you have?
Can you tell me?
Can we face it together?
Please.
Let me go.
Shen Suhe.
I won't let you go.
I'll wait until you tell me the truth.
You must have received
the news that the Western Shu Mission
has come to seek peace.
Yes.
This time,
they want to form a matrimonial alliance
with us
to end the decades of war.
I'd like to hear
your thoughts on this marriage.
I believe
that through this marriage,
we can end the conflict with Western Shu
and bring peace to the border regions.
It would be
a great benefit to the nation and its people.
I agree.
I have previously informed you
that the Princess of Western Shu has specifically requested
for you to be her consort.
She will be visiting with the diplomatic mission.
You will be in charge of
receiving the mission.
Your Majesty,
I'm just a soldier.
I'm afraid I'll neglect the mission.
You'd better...
I
entrust you with this task
because I trust you.
Besides,
you're not young anymore.
It's time to consider your marriage.
[My elder brother died.]
[My father died.]
[I've tried so hard,]
[but I can't change their fate.]
[In my dream,]
[although Prince Yu appeared by my side]
[after I was expelled to Lingguo Temple,]
[he had nothing to do with me.]
[But this time,]
[he has been by my side from the beginning.]
[It was his appearance]
[that made me have an illusion about fate.]
[But it seems that the ending can't be changed.]
[The Queen Mother will die.]
[I will also die.]
[Who is the person who killed the Queen Mother and me?]
[If I can find him,]
[can I end this wrong dream?]
My Lady.
My Lady, something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Something happened to Consort Dowager Li.
Consort Dowager?
It's about Prince Wu'an.
I heard that the Princess of Western Shu
has fallen in love with him.
This time, the envoy to Dakuai
is ostensibly for peace talks,
but actually,
it's to lure our Prince Wu'an over
to be their Imperial Son-in-Law.
Miss,
do you think His Highness will really marry
the Princess of Western Shu?
It's none of my business.
Miss,
I can tell that you have feelings
for Prince Yu,
right?
If he really marries the princess,
wouldn't you be sad?
Would you marry her?